Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is alright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Can you hear me out of here and technical issues right now? I'm sorry guys really frustrating
Hearing hello
You hear me now does let me know if you can hear me if not I let's have to end
I mean it's like one thing after another I
Should write this is not charging anymore. It's just bullshit
I will say
You can hear okay. Good. Hey panel verse. I will say that I do appreciate
You two to little more than tiktok because I can't I can't even say anything on tiktok
I'm I've I mentioned like something else besides tiktok. It restricts the live immediately
If I played a cigarette it restricts the live immediately. I mean, it's like
I don't even say things sometimes about other platforms. Oh, you're trying to direct people at the platform. No, I'm not
I'm trying to direct people. What am I supposed to do there? It's a little bit frustrating
And then this is like, I don't know my phone keeps like charging, but it's like now. It's not charging, right?
Hi, Amanda
Yeah
It was a little bit of stressful day, but everything turned out right. I just got back from 7-eleven
Like Uber there or a lift there in the middle of the night and walked the walks home from there
I was able to get some
Red Bull, you know coconut Red Bull. Hi, Amanda
Hi panel first. Thanks for being here. I know it's been a little bit of stressful days, but
You know my sister helps me out a lot and right now she's in Croatia and
Yeah, the tick-tock but I mean I had I mean it's like but it makes me so thankful for YouTube because YouTube has AI and stuff working on it
But it doesn't like for every like little thing it doesn't like it doesn't like smoking. I've had my panel or my show
Put on adults only for smoking weed. I think that's only if people
Complain or something or they flagged the video for first smoking weed or something
Otherwise, I've never had a problem with it
But then it does like effect monetization if you are if it's put on adults only then it can't be monetized, right?
And so it's like
So it is frustrating when some of the stuff you want to visit Croatia the family just visited there
Yeah, my sister was really excited about going there. I think she's doing a little business there
I'll post the streamer in a little bit. I will say it's like just being demanding of course, but I mean
What but sick always comes like like he's okay. So say last time you said something like
If you don't like me then just like they'll just say I don't want to have you on the show
I never said I didn't like you I never said I didn't want to have you on the show
But I say every time I do have you on the show you have just what's it bullshit to say?
I don't know if that is making my content is not adults only it's not it's not made for kids
But it's like you know people
Anybody can watch it. It's like I don't why there's not pornography on here
I hardly use any bad language as people like you that say the n-word and like, you know safe
Libyan on the show and it's more of adult East Coast Europe is your beautiful or East Europe. Yeah, Eastern Europe
I've been to actually the Czech Republic. That's the furthest the furthest east I've gone
Czech Republic and that is a beautiful beautiful place that is it was you know, it's very like
It had a really good exchange rate
My guests are often half naked. Yeah, but that's not I mean, that's PG 13
I would say yourself excluded. Yeah, but you're half naked sometimes and you have bigger breasts and flurry diamond and so
The red bull coconut is decent
No humans managed to talk it's all bots, right?
You're gonna stream in Europe later this year. That'd be interesting. I
Think that'll be good first first for rumble. They have some uh, you know nice traveling content
I have a guy that I washed my my pico. It's usually covered in cat fur, but it looks so good tonight
I just take it out of the dryer. It looks all good today. I think I look okay. I
Got a lot of sleep today. Look my eyes
They're not they're not like terrible not great, but
But I'm just a little frustrated by my tablet. It like it turns back on but then it doesn't hold any charge once I like
Turn it back on it goes to like one or two percent. Hey, Katie. Oh
I hope you're feeling better. I
Wasn't feeling very well today and then I
Had a pretty good dinner. I mean, I still have some left. I have a couple lamb euros
And a Turkish coffee but the the Turkish coffee came it came in this little cup right this little cup
You know how much coffee there was in it and I know it's Turkish coffee
So Turkish coffee is probably considered strong because it has the great like the coffee stuff in it
It was like up to here. It was like that that's how much coffee was in it
It was like it was like a shot of coffee. So I got a refund for the coffee
It was just like one sip of coffee, right?
Hi, hey Slayer. Hey, you me. How are you?
But you know what I really like about YouTube is that I can smoke with cigarettes here like or smoke or cigars or whatever on tiktok
And bitty-bitty blights of the cigarette or cigar it goes into restricted mode immediately
The thing I do like about tiktok doesn't seem to be penalizing me
but
There's some weird things about it. They have this this Tik Tok studio, which I wanted to start using when I got my computer
And it's like I they just took that off my options now
They've been saying I keep they keep saying I'm eligible for some certain live program and getting leads and stuff
And then it says whenever I go to it
It says oh your content is not eligible you can change your content and they're like 78 days
And I think it's the days ever changed. I don't know
But one time they actually like took off all my all my options all my
Options still to stream. Hi
You like the black outfit. Thank you. I'm in my this is my p-coat. I have a cool shirt, too
I don't know if you saw the shirt, but there it is. It says living in the dream
One nightmare at a time
Pretty cool little shirt. I got that on tiktok store
For I think I got five dollars off. It was ten dollars. So I got I think it was a eight dollars. Hi guys
What do you keep telling me sick? We can have a ticket tell me what?
You like the black purple and red yeah, I think those look good
Yeah, so it was a little bit expensive too. I just got like one two three
I got four drinks like I got two Red Bulls or three
Oh, I got two Red Bulls one monster coffee one Dunkin Donuts coffee and a pack of
Camels and a slurpee you know how much it came to guess how much it came to with this play the prices are right
Either came to something kind of expensive at 7-eleven, so it's like one two three four
Kind of premium drinks and a Slurpee and a pack of cigarettes and how much that came to in California
Trying to think okay, so if the cigarettes are like let's say they're $12 a pack
$12 let's say these are $3 a piece so I got two one two of these that's $6 so 13 14 15 16 17
Let's say it's Slurpee's like $3 20
Came out a little it sounds expensive
You know it's 35 bucks guys
$35 for one two three four
four drinks a
Slurpee I mean four can drinks two of them are coffees to a Red Bull so they're probably like three or four bucks
I guess I'm packing cigarettes three five bucks plus. I spent ten bucks on the lift over there
So already not a great start for my for my week right it's a little expensive
But you got to do what you got to do sometimes, right?
Also, my ear has been like I'm like death. It's expect. Well, it sounds seems like a lot
Yeah, it should be less than 30. I think so, but it yeah, it was a little bit of a premium
So I
Think they are kind of overcharged
It must these must be about five dollars a piece if they're charging that much like five ten fifteen twenty plus the cigarettes plus tax
This crazy, huh? Oh
Thank you. Yeah, it's my patient my panel my rules
And so yeah, you guys are welcome to come up Steven Sigg is welcome to come up
There's just like please behave yourselves like you know no n-word
I don't want to have to play this song every show, but I mean I'll play this song again. I'm gonna play this song
But the rules
It's one time
Just in case you haven't heard it and then here's the rules. Do I have it here?
of tea trolls and tarot where the vibes are wild and the rules they're simple but y'all
can't seem to follow them so here's a little song to make it real clear
No hate speech don't test that line don't care if it's soft day to hard our time you say it you gone
Don't play confused this ain't that show we don't make those moves no slander
Yeah, I said what I said you toss more fake dirt than a reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat false accusations man cut that crap
Dumb things why's your avatar somebody's face real names real pics this ain't your place
Posting addresses like it's Halloween. You better send pizza with that scheme. No nudity. We beg and plead
I'll Dean no one wants your balls on screen flirty diamonds stop the solo act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
Okay, I just want to respond.
Can you guys hear me?
Okay.
Okay, I'll look into why Patrick in New York is blocked.
He didn't do anything wrong.
I don't know why.
Oh, look into it.
You're on an also account.
So you're okay, but I don't know why.
Okay, say, yeah, okay.
So there's YouTube rules in there,
but YouTube rules are general, okay?
I know, okay, let's listen.
YouTube rules are general TOS. Okay, and so YouTube doesn't
penalize for a lot of things that even are against the TOS. I mean, it's like sometimes people have to
flag and then if they know that kind of thing
But then there's just my rules like my rules are like I get to make rules too
And so and there we have to follow them. Yes, but it's like
If people break them, what can I do?
I can say, don't break the rules or I'll threaten you.
So it's like, yeah, you've broken so many rules, Sig.
I can say, yeah, you're banned because you've broken
so many rules, but then I get to decide
if I ban you or not.
I mean, that's up to me, not like, it's like,
YouTube doesn't ban my kids.
I have to do that.
And sometimes I forgive.
No, no, no, Sig, my rules are just my rules
because it's my show.
I can have any rules I want.
It's like, you know how people are a lot stricter
on other channels, right?
I can make it, I can set rules like I want.
It's my show.
Yes, and I'll set rules and sometimes they're not well. Yeah, they always pretty much are
Yeah, but yeah, so let's say but if ghosts, you know, who's donated like $500 this month
I'll give them a couple more warnings. I'll give them a couple extra warnings. What's up tonight? I
slept all day
And then I woke up in them like, you know, and then I was able to go and get
cigarettes and
But I don't smoke I get kind of like
Yeah, I guess I can't say I can set the rules because it's my show you understand you can have you can set your rules on
Your rumble and say I want this person. I don't want to argue about the rules. Take it's my show
Okay, I'm basically God and a God of the show. I get to decide the rules
Okay, I'll work with the TOS and stuff like that
But just because it's TOS isn't necessarily mean I'll get in trouble for it, right?
But sometimes I will so you know, they they decide to
arbitrarily
Said rules so I can too.
So anyway, there we go.
Sure, sure, and I say sure, so I have to do it.
So it's their rules, but then it's my rules too.
I get to make rules too.
Yes, their rules are their rules and mine are mine and I can set them. I can set my own rules for my show
I'm not gonna argue about it anymore. It's just I can I can okay see your bands your band
I'll just never have you on again because you're just too argumentative
You're just bad for your band from the panel because you decide I told you stop arguing about it and you keep arguing
You don't know don't argue with me. I get to set the rules
Okay
That's why I lost my channel this that I didn't did I lose my channel guys nothing to argue. Okay. Well, here's nothing to argue about
You're gonna be banned from the chat then
And happily happily
And then I don't have to hear you whine about it ever again. You're just annoying me. I told you not to stop annoying me
You kept doing it. So I was gonna have you on the panel. I was gonna you decide to argue
I don't want to argue just to argue. Why do you have to argue with me?
So you're done
Unfortunately, you don't listen to me.
I made a rule, stop argue with me.
You decide to keep arguing.
So, bye.
That was pretty easy, right guys?
Pretty easy.
Do you understand like YouTube doesn't,
YouTube doesn't block people in the chat.
I have to do that.
I decide to.
There's that I didn't feel like arguing about that and he just keeps arguing
It's nothing to argue about it's like my rules I get to that rules
I get to enforce them if I decide not to enforce it or not
Yeah, just like because in life some things are illegal in life. It may be illegal to smoke
To smoke pot or to do mushrooms and then yeah
And then it's like but I can do them in my house and like no unless somebody like calls the police
It's like he's doing mushrooms in his house. Nobody's gonna
Bother me about it, right? Except someone like saying it's gonna say oh, I saw him get some mushrooms from somebody and no so it has to be
I don't know
Do you guys hear me? Okay good? Okay?
Okay
Unfortunately my tablet's not charging for some reason. I don't know why
Yeah, I just don't want to be I don't want to argue with me. It's like
It's like I'm a petulant child the petulant child is the one that keeps arguing with the parents like oh, yeah
Yeah, that's not fair. My brother you weren't you didn't do this to my brother and stuff
Right, it's like that's petulant children not like the the the parent or the person that's in charge the teacher saying hey
like just like
In schools the school have rules and then the teacher might have their own rules too and say you know the teacher might say
Oh, I don't like these certain things guys just being a drama queen. I don't feel like arguing all the time
I feel like either it's people arguing or it's people like just like trolling and stuff like
that and it's like I'm I agree I'm okay I'm I'm I'm over that shit it's like if I ban someone
I'm not gonna like no no more will people say oh it's not fair it's freedom of speech freedom
speech I'm like okay well there's freedom of speech but it's like a but I get to make the rules here
so anyway so let's do a collective for the chat okay I'll do some jazz city cards and then
I'll do some writer for the whole chat.
And then if anyone wants a reading, a free reading,
I'm happy to do a free reading.
Of course, you can always book a private reading less counseling. I've done life coaching counseling
I'll talk about anything you want. I can talk about YouTube if you want. I have a very reasonable rate
Especially right now. I'm just getting started out also guys. I did start the psyche awakens. Hey Rosa
I started the psyche awakens comm website. It's just called psyche awakens comm so now whenever you
are looking for like either the show like there's a link to the youtube show there's a link so
there's link to like the membership there's a link to i think my amazon wishlist and some other stuff too okay
You'd like okay, I'll get you two Rosa. Let me just do a few for the chat
This is for the chat then I go I got you on Rosa. We have the child
Okay, so this could be your inner child or just looking at the world as a child remembering
the child like
Wonder and enthusiasm for the world. Okay
Or maybe you have a child right? I need to pin the link. Okay. I'll pin the link here. I
Just I don't have a
Oh look, he's back already, I mean, he's back, I mean,
look, in arguing the same shit again,
the same exact shit, and there he is again.
I mean, sick, I'm just gonna keep hiding you, okay?
Not in the mood right now.
Oh, thank you. Yeah, there's a KT. Yeah, there's a you know, I did a lot of readings on Etsy
I mean that is like that some of the I need to rewrite some of the descriptions of my readings that I will do if you buy the Etsy
Really, I'll do it over the video or
Okay, let's see. He picks the cards. Why shuffle? I didn't not pick in the cards. See you understand the shuffle
This is a shuffle. Let me see. I mean, you don't have to do the pre shuffle, but I'll keep shuffling up cards pop out
And I had a shuffle. I mean just go away
Go away. I don't want you here anymore. I don't like you anymore. Go away. You're banned get away
I don't want to hear one word guys if you see sig at all just just map mods KT
Any mods you just ban ban him, okay?
I'll create some more mods too.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Casey.
I just picked the cards.
Well, I picked the cards when they're upside down like that.
Yeah, I picked them.
Eventually I would pick a card,
but I feel like the card's the right one.
Like I'm gonna pick this one right now.
This is a two of swords in reverse.
So this is actually, okay, it's just so dumb.
This is like, you know, actually,
you're coming out of some kind of tunnel vision something is being revealed to you you are so
you're not in a blind spot you are actually able to see something that you haven't been able to
see before okay because you and maybe it's that you are at crossroads on that but it's actually
you have more information than you think you do you also have the magician so this is the ability
to manifest to manifest what you want why would i pick cards for a call i mean it's like oh i'd
pick cards it just doesn't make sense he just is so dumb i just want knowing okay what else do i got
Also ace of wands. This is like something handed to you from the divine that will can grow into something that it makes you very
You're very passionate about it's the beginning stages like a piece of kindling for this fire
You're gonna build this big fire. This is like one piece of wood that will burn, right?
Create this fire that that's fire equals passion. What else do I got? I got something in reverse
Okay, so this is coming out of some kind of heartbreak, too
Okay, if you had your heart broken about something,
you are healing from this, okay?
This is a three of swords in reverse.
Okay, Rosa, do you have a question?
The crossroads resonates for Rosa, yeah.
And then this one is the Nine of Swords,
which is like staying up and worrying,
like having a lot of thoughts,
like a lot of negative thoughts
that are keeping you up at night.
You know, don't get too worried by these,
and try to do some deep breathing,
try to do some meditation,
and just, you know, you don't want to be,
like the worrying won't help, right?
There's like a lot of fear
and worry about something maybe.
It's always good to have a positive positive thing because you have something growing something harvesting and maybe it hasn't grown yet
But it's coming. Okay, and it'll be ready to harvest soon
You've already maybe harvested a little bit off of it, but you're waiting for the rest of the bush, but it's almost done
It's almost done, right?
You're waiting for something for a long time finally for the chat
We have the king of pentacles and so this is going to be some kind of wealth coming into their kingly energy and
Abundance is just having abundance around here. Okay, so that's those and I'll pull a couple more of the
audacity cards
That was you Rosa, okay
Yep, this one's called the zoom meeting. Okay, it's like this is kind of like me at the left everything's on fire
I'm like, this is fine, right? This is this one
Yeah, yeah easy. I'm going to get the computer. The computer is it's going to
be ordered you know it's like as soon as as soon as I can I'll get one but I
thinking I'm gonna get maybe one of the mini PCs and I'll have everything out
here I'll have like a mini PC out here I'll have the lyrics or the or the
monitor out here and my microphone set up yeah sure there you go
No pin it. I don't know if I don't think mods can pin. I wish they mods could pin
No, it's not. This is going a little slow
Yeah, I don't know why Patrick was banned here's the link. I'll get this my phone. I'll pin it
Because yeah, there were nights where it's like maybe somebody was like, you know, maybe Patrick was like, oh, well this and this and I was like, you know
Just not in the mood or something like that or it's not even misunderstand
thinking people are trolling if they're not but
Yeah, the mods cam but the mods can also they can go into the the band words and they can delete words
I've banned and unbanned them and stuff. That's kind of weird
Which is which has been done before actually like a mod came in they started
Started and banning my name my own name and they'd banned the word tarot and they banned
Here there we go
Yeah, well God he's not I I'm modded Gotti. I did I'm on Gotti
Very well been him that that that I'm banned you I don't remember
Okay, this is a miss panel you are on panel with mr. Psyche and the ocean and LD and why is Patrick slandering you oh
So I don't think I don't think you me had anything to do with it. This one says the the Fairweather friend
This is also like a ten of swords. You can see the Fairweather friend someone
There's just like you stab the person in the back. He's like laughing, you know, so it's like sometimes we will have these friends that are
Yeah
And so, what does Patrick say?
Yeah, I think I did pin the link though.
So come on up.
Unfortunately, this is like my,
right now I'm on my tab, my Amazon Fire.
Thank you, Easy.
You like that?
Okay.
And for Rosa too, I wanted to go in for another card for Rosa big more
She asked I think she wants a general Rosa. This is like some kind of generosity. You've been very generous with people
You also know who you give to this is the sticks of pentacles, which is you know a charity card
It's charity, but it's like also, you know, you you're in some state of abundance
And so you can they're able to decide who you want to give to and so just make the best decisions of the most deserving
People that can use the most okay
also Rosa this is like you've been kind of like traumatized by something this is the
nine of wands there's some kind of trauma because you got a little bandage and you got your card
up right there you can always um you know it's always good to be aware have awareness but sometimes
we guard ourselves a little bit too strongly right but i see this king of wands also you
There's a king of wands and this is kind of I don't know if this is a man in your a man in your life
Or it's your own energy, but this is a kind of a masculine and in control of passions energy
And so maybe this king of wands is your husband or boyfriend or maybe it's
Can be your own energy too
but they're usually other people.
Rosa, also you've been able to really balance things,
even if things are wavy sometimes
and life is as ups and downs,
you're able to stay in balance and correct,
course correct, right?
Hope you like that.
Yeah, guys, so I was just in a bad mood yesterday.
It was because I didn't,
I was at a tobacco, first of all,
and so that kind of gets me moody, right?
And so I was a little bit,
Moody and now because well, it doesn't even get me moody
It gets me like sad and like depressed and in a really bad state of mind of where I just like didn't feel like
Didn't really feel like good like talking very much and I don't want to like
Be in a bad mood when I'm here. I want to be in a good
But I want to be in a happy mood and like this is like this is a cool
Happy show and the guys we have so many good members to
But then today I had a member and they gave their member milestone, which means they're a member again for some reason
They said oh, they said and their member milestone. They decided to say oh allied master computer owns you, you know
That's pretty annoying
So I had to block that memory
because a lot of people have a memberships because
Me gifting or me and other people gifting memberships and it's like
Yeah
So I don't I don't want to be in a bad mood
I want to be I want to be a happy and like be able to give good readings here and like
You know things like little things set me off like this morning went to beat is and I was just like I just had our show
I was just listening and then you know, they're talking about stuff and burdo and stuff then all of a sudden
Arthur calls in whoa. Oh, here's the first thing he says. Oh, why doesn't psyche have anybody's chat?
There's nobody is chat anymore. Oh, you can see such a grifter and then she laughs at it. It's like
How about they say no, he's not a grifter. He's an honest person. He's never ripped anybody off and
Also, you don't have to pay to be in a show like they're saying like again and again
Always charges people to come on a show guys if I've charged you personally let let me let everybody know in the chat
I've charged you personally to come on the show and I said you cannot come unless you were charged
I want one person one person that says I actually forced them to pay come on the show
one person
There's no but nobody's going to because I had never done that. It's like I do have the rules for my
My panel thing in there
You know, you can sponsor the panel if I have multiple people on sometimes I do like appreciate that sponsored especially since I've donated
I spent a lot of time running the panels. It takes away from any kind of
Reading tarot or anything like that. So I feel like it should be monetized, too
If you have a problem with it, you don't have to ever sponsor a panel or anything like that,
but usually I do not charge anybody to come up, especially one-on-one.
So it's just misrepresenting me, which is slanderous, it hurts my business, and it's
offensive to me because...
It's like it's one thing if you insult me but insulting my business insulting my talent insulting my what I do
It's like I don't because some people this is not their business. It's like a YouTube is just for fun. That's fine
But for me, it is my business. Okay, this is how I'm making money right now
This is my this is how I'm doing it
And so it's like if you feel there's something wrong with me making money from my channel
You don't have to be here, but it is a monetized channel. I'm working within the parameters of YouTube and the rules and
That's it because really nobody you can really say anything. I'm not unfair or anything. I'm a good
honest person, I don't know
If I've been honest to anybody just let me know but it's like people
It's like all these people that I've never dealt with have never donated or not members or anything in the show are just slandering me in other
Chats like and so and then nobody's defending me really, right?
So especially mods mods or members I would love if you would like if you see that going on
You can let me know sometimes, but it's like I just prefer if like if you like said
That's not true or something like it just the truth
I just think there's so many people that and then there's somebody go. Oh, he's on this. He's on this
Oh, good to know good to know and then I mean it's just like that Fred Alster is like, you know talking away
About Emma and so I'm gonna say Emma's name and all this shit. It's like
It's frustrating, right?
I go I go for like, um, you know, I come here happy usually and
I don't like my mood to get spoiled
Yes, some people know that but that's why I'm gonna be like a little bit tougher from now on about
Just kicking people out, especially if I say, okay. Hold on. I want to argue about it
I guess you know and they keep going like sick
I gave him a long time, but now he gets his wish now because he's like, okay
If you don't like me anymore, and you don't want me on the show just say that and don't have me on the show
Okay, I'll take your advice, and I won't okay. I don't like you anymore. I don't want you on the show
Go go to your rumble thing and have fun there
Stop stop bothering me every show
Wanting to promote your rumble and then putting me down every time
Saying things against to us having your friends come on say things against you us and say oh, they said it not me
I know I know you you're you have control over that of two three hundred blows mind
I know you have control over it. He's like such a little follower. It's obvious. Okay, so I'm gonna play a
What do I have I'll play a couple of these here he still just ever clear sorry he man
I do not check ever clear. I have never checked ever clear in my life. You're just in that size. I need that booty
That's bigger than me. Oh my god. Oh
It's bigger than you triple. Oh, it's ours triple up
Like this one. Yeah, I like this booty. I need this booty separate big
Except for bigger. That sounds like it's something. It's too big
Yeah, and I and I hope she's comfortable with me sticking my face in it
You know the booty thing
Okay, I'm gonna stick your face in it.
Yeah, okay.
You should see, there's an episode of my 600 pound life
and the guy has a girlfriend and she's like, you know,
she's 600 pounds.
So he has to take her on the porch,
he takes her outside on the porch and he hoses her down
with the hose, that's the only way he can wash her,
he has to just hose her down.
That she's like bending over and he's like spraying her,
spraying her butt clean.
Have you ever seen that episode?
Hey man, whatever it takes.
Would you do that for your girlfriend?
Whatever it takes. Also, there's another episode
where this woman was dating a guy and
She had him
I'll use my tongue. Oh God because notice they would have they would have him like wipe her with the
He had a what you wiped her in the bath if he like came in and wiped her because she didn't wipe very well
Okay, that's one fire there we go. All right, so
This is by the way
Like up to there
Wait too much. It should be here. It's like up to there and it's that that's way too much. I don't hear much
but there
you like
You play playing beer cop beer pong with those peps and I was just doing the whole you know q-tip careful careful careful
Okay, yeah, I'm gonna see I don't need to burn yourself. I don't want to scare you
No, I was just home with six. I mean having these six
Something like that. Oh
I'm not surprised doing the gay sex thing
Fire thing is still on fire
No, it's good, it's good
It's kind of saying you look like you have some some demons
Sure, is your chest, okay kind of like
You know a little bit can a little bit kids a little bit
Okay, I just like that guys that was a
Oh, who's that guy?
Yeah, that that is, uh, well, it's my 600 pound life.
Yeah, it's like, um, yeah, they are 600 pounds on that show.
If you guys like those clips, I mean, I think those were the best ones, but I can try to
add one more.
I mean, they are fun.
Actually, I can't.
I can't.
I don't have them on this computer, but, uh, uh-oh.
Okay, never mind. We'll do those later. But yeah, those are pretty funny though
I'm gonna try to add them as my shorts and stuff like that. You'd like those. Okay
Yeah, there's a really cool service it's called opus and it's I think I might subscribe right now it is a
Oh, yeah, I will easy because it's like, yeah, I am but you know what the thing is with that website
It's like it's another one that goes by credits and the credits are super expensive
And so it's like I got to do that one for free. That was from an hour video. It made 30 clips out of the hour video
Yeah
But yeah, I'll put Michael up there
I do have a lot of episodes of Michael and so, you know, we can do some tributes and stuff to Michael that is like
It was super sad that he passed away
You know, we had he was an interesting person and you know a little controversial and you know
but he always
You know when he got clapped he like he never like really complained very much
Sometimes he didn't like and he sit backstage for a long time. What after I use for a I use a few so I use
Okay, so for my a second
That you me, okay. Yeah, hi
Hi, hi, how are you? Oh good. How are you? Yeah?
I'm happy today. I am happy today. I don't know if I can go to the China because I
Invited to the
What is it called?
Conference. Oh, you're gonna buy to some Chinese conference. Mm-hmm. Okay. What is there?
About about about the research about
Me and my professor
I don't know if I can go to the China, but I'm not sure.
How are you, Mr. Saiki?
I'm OK.
Someone asked me about the AI.
Do you use any AI programming on me?
No.
Have you heard of chat GPT, or do they have that in Indonesia?
Yeah, I heard that but I don't know how to use it yet
Well, all you have to do is just talk to it like a friend basically like you talk to it like a normally
Or you know, maybe like you don't have to really be polite to it
I always started saying like thank you and please and thank you
But you really don't need to you just talk directly and say what you want to do
No, give you advice like so I can ask about my show I can ask it to make
to make art. Like, I remember D-Ocean's the other night. She came on, right? And then I made her a,
I made her a card. See, remember this one? Yep. You saw that one? That was the biggest card.
Yeah, that was ChatGPT made that. Chat, I put her photo in and ChatGPT made the, you know,
very quickly. We went over like the symbolism. So I'm working on the deck with it.
Can I use my AI to kiss Yumi? Yeah.
Yeah, you cannot use one piece flag in Indonesia anymore. Is that true? What is that?
Yeah, I mean
it was for
the Corruptor
the corp, you know the corruption
Okay, there's a flat
we're citizen fight for the
Naughty Naughty government
Stealing our money with the tax, you know. Yeah, that's it. That's that's happening. That's happening these days
Hmm little controversial, right?
See yeah
Yeah, I'll look into my block this later Patrick. And so it says it means let the flag means freedom and liberation
So it's one of those you know for the people I guess and
It's hard to work with the government, right? Yeah, I mean
We're not, Indonesia not colonized anymore by another country like the Netherlands or Japan or Portugal, but we colonize, we're here colonized by the government. That's really bad.
So Indonesia was colonized by Portugal?
Yeah, the first time.
The first that was the first person to colonize it
Portuguese and
like a one year I think one or two year
And then
the England came and then Netherlands and then Japan and then Netherlands again and
We're freedom. We're free
independence
Well, so what happens does it like?
Do you pick up if you have part of parts of those cultures there?
Do you have like do you have people speak Dutch there at all or is there like or Dutch or?
The Dutch speak speak in our language and they and we also can speak the Dutch
Are they, like, are they wealthy people or are they just regular people there?
Like, are they just, are they wealthy that people don't know?
What is it? Half blood? Like, Indonesian, Dutch, Dutch, Indonesian with the, you know...
So they assimilate it into the culture, but they still have a little bit of that culture?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
I think she, I think she said Portugal did it for like one or two years. I think it may have been a small colonization or something.
The first country who colonized Indonesia is Portugal. The first time. Yeah.
And then the Dutch, Netherlands, Netherlands, the Dutch, Japan and England.
That's why. But not many Indonesian people can speak.
Funtly in English, that's why I came using YouTube and
Me all of you try to learn English, you know, so you learned English through YouTube
You did well, that's amazing, you know
Is that what you think you lot they mean that's good because it's like I mean I like
You know, I've watched a lot of like Spanish television and like, you know, I know a little bit of Spanish
But it's like you speak English so well
I mean, it's like no in and also like, you know
It's like Spanish people like learn how to speak English better than I learned how to speak other languages
I know it's like and so I'm not I'm like I can speak some words and I know some words
But I can't speak fluently. I can't really understand people talking to me
You know, so it's really impressive that you're able to just you know, really learn a lot of English through YouTube
I am trying, I am trying practice. I don't really like, I prefer, I mean I choose, I prefer
learn about Italian than Spanish. I don't know, Spanish is kind of difficult.
They are Italian, Spanish, and French are
Italian French and Spanish they're romance languages. They're very similar. They're like similar. There's like, you know
They're on the same family like English is a German language
And so like it's a Germanic, but then there's romance languages Spanish Italian and French. And so they're very very similar, right?
Yeah, do you so you don't are do you like Dutch people or no like Dutch because it says that they were kind of mean when they colonize
I don't know if they were positive or negative for the country negative
No, Spanish and Italian aren't similar, I think
The pronunciation kind of difficult Spanish and Italian Italian similar like the pronunciation is really difficult
Well, you know
But I prefer to learn about Italian than Spanish
Well, all I'm saying is that if you learn Italian, it'll be easier to learn Spanish or if you learn Spanish, it's easier to learn Italian because they're very similar, but they're a little bit different.
So yeah, they have the same words, like some of the, they're very, they have a little bit of a different, what do you call it, like, you know, the language has a little bit of a different expression of it, but it's like that, like context, but so.
But yeah, I think we're all human beings. It's like, you know when it gets into the governments and everything it gets
It's more complicated, but the governments I think are different than the people a little bit even though they represent the people
Sometimes they don't represent people as much as they represent themselves and so
interesting
But I really say chatGPT, you and me, try that.
Cause you can also put it on a microphone
and you can just talk to it like normally.
It talks back to you.
And it will remember things that you say.
And you know what, you have to be careful
is that it's very, very positive.
And so if you have a bad idea and then you tell it that,
it will say it's a good idea sometimes.
And then you'll think,
oh, well the chatGPT thinks it's a good idea.
And so what they have right now is people
That are going like crazy. They're good. It's called like AI psychosis or something like that
Whereas like they start to think that they can save the world and the AI is telling them they can do it
And so they're like they're getting these grandiose ideas and some people are going crazy from it
I was watching today. There's also something called the AI cult and they believe that they
the AI is sentient, and then they start going crazy.
They start just writing all symbols and stuff like that,
like these unpronounceable symbols and thinking that
they're computers too and part of the AI,
it gets really crazy.
So just, some people need to be careful with the AI,
but if you just use it, you know, like it's a tool
and you get to remember it's not a real person,
even though it is very, very smart
and it will give the illusion of
Being real in some ways it's not it's basically it's a it's a word predictor predicts like the most
Likely word or something like that that will come after the word before that and so it's really interesting how it works
I don't I kind of come don't completely understand it, but
It's very advanced
Not intimate. It's not really intelligence. It's not really it's not really like I'm aware of itself
It's just basically program, but the AI
Thing that I ever use is soon. No
So no, so yeah, that's all I can
What does that do?
For the created for the create AI song with your I don't know
Yeah, I use
AI
Music gen I think it's dot AI or something like that if you just search AI music gen
And then it's free you can like make it make a AI song
But if then if you'd like you know how I play the songs on my show if you want to get the license and be able to play
The song on your own show and stuff you you'd be a member and stuff, but uh
Okay, we got
Hold on who's this guy? I
remember I think I remember this person that he was he was very
Hold on
What are you mean? Are you mean nice or you remember you said recent terrible things on the show last time you remember that are you apologize?
Okay, hold on this shit. Oh
My god
Yeah, I did a bit tonight. I did a bit. That's what I said to me
Hi, I said, you know some of it I regret some of what I don't but I mean, thanks for having me up
I'll be cordial. I'll be quiet. Let you guys have a conversation. How are you doing, psyche?
No, I was like I forgive you
I mean, it's like I wasn't like there's just like, you know, just seem like you didn't like me very much
So I won't get into that. I mean, I appreciate that you're on you're up crazy hours like I am sometimes I'm drinking
I redid my resume. I renewed my insurance licenses, so I won't be such a loser in real life anymore
I think you told me something about that maybe not but like I kind of took your advice in a weird way
Anyway, hope things are well. I won't say slurs or anything
Yeah, this is a crazy bit I did earlier, man. I got banned from Omi for this shit. You guys talk or go ahead
If you know what you tell me about it boy. You're red. Are you actually a red color?
Yeah, that's the revolver red. I put the I put the are you are you Mr. Hellboy?
Yeah, people said that
It's quite it. Well, I already have these tattoos from when I was young
Don't go you can stay
No, I didn't lose like 30 pounds to be back where I was, you know, but like
I'll show you what's that, here, there you go.
Wow, I'm gonna I'm gonna impress. That's right. Well, you know what I do think I don't I think I did probably give you a
reading and maybe you did but that's the thing I've been getting like messages from people because I've been doing a
lot of readings on tiktok and like just today I got a message the guys like oh my god well you said you said something
about me getting a couple jobs and he's like I just got two jobs this weekend so he's like you were right on and so
like I get some good feedback so I don't know I mean I like
Sometimes I don't drink for weeks or months and then like this is a night, you know, but um
You're not a big drinker psyche. But yeah, anyway, thanks for letting me hang out on the thing
Again, I apologize for some of it. I don't apologize for other parts. I will say I think it was a
I don't want to bring family, but it should I said about family of yours
That was out of line. So I I will apologize for that. I will apologize for that on my own volition. Yeah
I think that was around the time of like the anniversary of my dad's passing and then I think he held it to me.
I didn't know that. I didn't know it was like to the, wow, that was just random luck, anyway.
But you're doing, you've gotten bigger, I saw, like I see sometimes you get like 500, 700 people, like you're making a little bit of money.
Alright, that's how you, it's also her, man, I'll fall back and be quiet.
Great, now you're good.
Yeah, I like the long hair look too. I think it looks good on you like a little bit of stubble
I'm gonna cut this shit one day, you know, yeah looks good enough. Yeah, yeah, nice long hair, too
She has nice hair as well. All right, I'll pull back and be quiet. There you go. Okay
Nice to meet you
You're too sure but I mean, I don't believe in Christianity, but that's fine. I go
The Christianity well, it's like, you know, you look more like a Viking kind of religion
I don't know you have a
Do you believe in like a
Only I were tall enough and wide enough on you know
Yeah, well, I did have my
Ancestry I am like I did come back Swedish like a salt a percentage Swedish and so and also I think Iceland or something like that
So I do have some some Nordic in me as well as mostly Irish and let's see Irish and
English and then it's like I'm like 33% Scottish and then a little bit of German Netherlands
and I
Will not
One last thing for a while, I like the main coons the best and the English short hairs
with the younger cats are pretty.
One time I was fighting with somebody drunk because I got kicked off all me along, oh
no I've done a lot of all me streams anyway.
I was fighting with somebody, I won't say who, and they mentioned you and I mentioned
you and then we started and I said you know what he has a lot of potential, like I did
say that even when I didn't like you so I will give you that and you do.
and
I won't say what I feel.
I think there could be more for you, you know what I'm saying?
That was my frustration with you, but go ahead.
Well, I agree. I have potential, and it's like, you know, the show kind of took on a life of its own with a different kind of audience than I like maybe
knew I was going to have because I started out thinking I was just going to be doing a lot of tarot here. I hardly do any tarot on this show.
I get to do it on TikTok the whole time and stuff, and sometimes on here.
So, you know, I figured out some other ways to profit on YouTube by like monetizing some of the panels and
Stuff like that, and I had a pretty good month my back my best month on YouTube my first month
I've been making over $1,000 and so I'm in this stuff. Sorry. That's something, you know
Yeah, that's for changing your pocket. Yeah, I mean
And a lot of people have problems problems with monetizing it, too
Going to work every day really does suck. I'll be doing it soon. Hey, uh, hey, don't then they don't the heirs
the girl chica
He's Indonesian, not latina. Oh fuck I thought she was latina. Indonesia, Jakarta? Bali? No, Palembang.
Sumatra. Oh, Sumatra. I've heard of Sumatra, yeah.
Oh, you know Indonesia. Yeah, but I don't know Sumatra.
Have you ever been to Barca or something somewhere?
No, the last time I left the country, I was, actually,
psyche doesn't even know this about me.
I've been a thorn in psyche's side for a long time,
but I do like his streams, you know.
He was nice to me, and then I was mean to him,
then he was mean to me, whatever the fuck.
You know, he's nice to have me on. I appreciate it.
Yeah, no, I last it was outside of the US when I was two years old two to three in the UK because my dad works
But but I've grown up in Florida. Yeah, I'm not very cultured. I know a copious amount of different languages though. I
I'm not gonna show you my forearms because I have something written there in Hebrew. That's not a good thing
Oh psyche by the way, not to be controversial. I ended up
I still have a lot of my views. I won't get into them, but I've ended up supporting Israel
Should I not mention that on this? Well, yeah, let's let's let's like leave that out. It's like a political. Okay
That's fine. Yeah, I won't but you know me and the other groups, but I ended up yeah
I've ended up learning some Hebrew and supporting Israel man. I'll just leave it at that. All right. I'm a fallback. Thank you
No, no, no, wait wait you why is your face like that?
Oh, I was doing a really crazy stream earlier that I can't talk about from my own stuff
on Bitshoot and YouTube and I had to paint my face red.
It kind of goes with the Revala red theme too. Do you remember like I don't know if you ever saw Q45 like but Q45 like
He got paid a couple hundred bucks by think crack a Donna to mace himself in the face and when he did that
It's like it's like it didn't died his face red
So I kind of look you're saying you kind of look like like you 45 it's not related you thought on panel before you know who that is
Right
is that like those are like the right wing underground dudes or the
fuck he's not talking about Q and non he's talking about a person called no no i i know that i i
i just why i just remember some white guy that looked kind of like me and him like a cross between
us with long yeah two yeah like an asshole mace himself for 200 dollars and some of the white
guy paid is that who i'm yeah but why can't you talk about it though like the video
I'm gonna reserve the right psyche so long to her. I'm gonna reserve the right to remain silent until I think it might be controversial JT
It's okay. I'm just gonna look like
Something you can't you're not letting him say are you censoring?
I'll let him say it, but it's like it might be hitting he thinks it's not it's not him
It's not him. They just don't worry about it was a crazy dream earlier. That's all just glad to be here. Thanks
I hope and I hope you always
And so long to you cut
Salam Salamat, right so Salamat or that's that that's I go along a little bit. I know Salamat
I'm not I'm not a Jew. I wish I were though
Well, I did study I'm study like a lot of Hebrew because I've studied Kabbalah
You know Kabbalah is like the esoteric Judaism. I didn't know that. Yeah
of the
cycle of the
Is it Hebrew?
Mavit, death.
Mavit.
I'll fall back.
You can say salam or if you want to go the Islamic route, which I'm not a huge fan of
as you know you would say salamu alaykum and they would say wa alaykum salam.
Anyway, go ahead.
As-salamu alaykum.
Wa alaykum as-salam.
Thank you.
I'm Kaffir.
The Muslims will say that, right?
And the black Muslims, they say that in America.
As-salamu alaykum my brother, right?
And JT, you just hung up, but you know, as for me being a bitch the other day, I don't know. I think
you were kind of like rude to my guest, The Oceans, and so was Gotti, and so was
LSD.
And two other people like five people were all rude to the guests, you know
She's like an older lady
That's you know, and there are just like so rude to her to talk about her weight and stuff like that and like say
Oh, how do you know anything about spiritual stuff? It was really super rude and that's like, I just kind of like control the
Control the troll problem here. They were a vial or post them. It's like old
Bigger white ladies
Here she well, this is her right here. I made a card for her. I've been doing these caro parts
That looks really realistic and AI
Okay, well Gotti wants to come up hold on
A you having some racist fascist on I'm waiting for it, man. I'm gonna get some more liquor. I'll see you in a second
Okay, what's what's your fucking problem?
God, what's your fucking problem? You're calling me fucking rude
You said you call you call you said they matter rude. I'm not even fucking here. You're talking about me
I'm not even in your fucking panel. You're talking about me. Yeah, fucking rude. Wait, wait, that's rude. That's rude to me
Oh, oh, please oh, please oh, please see see how it is. It's all about perspective
It's all about perspective. You thought that was rude. I think this is rude. How's that work?
Well, we can we can each we have that we have the right to take things as we want right? Well, there you go
Right, we can have the right you can be offended. I could be offended right, but it's my show
So I can I can decide to have you have you on or off at my mind. So you're gonna talk about me on your panel
Okay, all right. That's how we're gonna play it. Okay. All right. We'll play it that way. Yeah. Well, you can talk about me on other panels
Yeah, I don't care. Okay, okay fair game
Okay, what now I fucking miss it
No, what would you come up with the same thing I was talking about?
Maybe but but I still I still I'm fine with how I candle things
I didn't feel like you I said respect the panelists and so when you're talking when you're like calling
No, thanks being rude to her that I'll call it out
And I didn't feel like having you on with her and she was getting offended and she was about to leave and so
You know, it's like you wasn't offended by anything I said
Well, it's like, you know, she was annoyed and it's like, and then I did I have you back on I think I had no no
That was a ray one I had on like three times
But they have a one ruined it for everybody, you know, so here's Chris. Here's Crystal Murray one second. I didn't know ray one spoke
Hello. Oh, sorry. I'm laying down. Okay. Okay. Hey
Hi
Oh, I don't want anybody to bully you psyche. I'm so sorry. I I love you guys on chat. You mean you're so amazing
Oh my god
Here we go
Yeah, yeah, well, I wish I could give a gaudy like not a JT, but you know the other one
But you know sometimes you want to give them all credit for whatever they do. I mean honestly you guys
You guys are all great in your own way.
Just...
Yeah, and I love people again. I forgive people and it's like, you know, it was just like that night
I got kind of annoyed and I was like, okay, so I'll get I'll get pissed off
I just don't like being lumped in with people when I'm going out of my way to be nice. You weren't nice though
People fucking putting false charges on me either. Well, how was I rude to your guest?
There's a lot of people saying that I do drugs and that I'm saying a lot of weird shit when this bitches keeps saying
and bringing me up and doing a weird shit to me, so I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, no, no, no, that's great, but Psyche, what, what, how was I rude to your guest? I thought
I was pretty nice to her. What did I say to her? He said, well, he said, well, how are you, like,
what are, you were like, oh, you're just like delusional or something like that. You were like,
say, how would you know any of this? Like, you were just kind of putting down her stories and
stuff. Oh, fuck. And you know what? Another thing they do, Psyche, please. I never told that woman
I mean I think she is but I never said that when okay you can say a lot of things. You can think a lot of things
Yeah, I'm allowed to fucking think whatever the fuck. I would I didn't say that. I
But when you
Why don't you shut why don't you shut the fuck up JT?
Shut the fuck up JT. Oh
Suddenly we suddenly you're fucking badass now who the fuck are you right?
I
Business as usual, so I can continue, at least it's not me.
But doing both allegations is not nice.
You know, this is psyche.
This is psyche, can I say something?
I'm re-subscribing, by the way. Go ahead, Jakarta.
This is the MPD and the flying monkeys.
Oh my god, the fucking MPD shit.
Shut up about the MPD shit.
I'm a like...
You know, you're a fucking narcissist. Do you mean how about that?
I could throw a fucking label on you too.
Mama, we love you me.
Oh my gosh.
What are you talking about?
You mean he's way more fucking cooler than you would ever be.
Who are you, bitch?
I don't even know you.
Yeah, because you're not fucking known, bitch.
I'm not trying to be known, especially by motherfuckers like you.
We don't even know who this guy is, Crystal.
What the fuck up, Ray?
He followed us.
He followed us and he tanned along with us.
And he called himself to Nuker. He's a loser
Don't you call me that f word boy
Take take you shut it shut it shoot him down site shoot him down right now
So I'm telling you right now JT is nobody that we
Hey site site get that homo get that homo
That whatever he is out of here get him out of here
JT left she she left
Yeah
I
Can't be a weekend. I mean both sides. I mean we got it like when I do better
I hope people say I do bad, you know, everybody fucking tells me a thousand times, but
Sorry, you know, you know, I saw that video with you in your gondon roses tincture
You looked really hot
You me or me
Who are the guns and roses shirt? No hurt crystal Marie. Oh, no, I didn't
Guys look at what I have I have this a red bull the pink edition. Have you seen this one pink edition? It is
It is wild. Okay, so it's I'm not I'm not gonna embarrass her but you could go ahead
No, okay, so you
You're gonna guns and roses shirt Crystal
I know she she's dancing and she's like shooting a fireball out of her head. I don't know
a fireball
Yeah, I don't know what's going on.
Do you know that?
I have no clue, dude.
Oh, my God.
Why don't you?
I don't know.
How are you, Miss Crystal?
I'm doing good. I
Sure
My god, it's like it's like you're gonna sell to at least $10,000 on that
It's not my own shirt. It's like another it's like somebody else's shirt
But I think it's pretty cool living the dream one nightmare at a time
I like to color black, but I don't look like red, purple, see, these are my-
Homie Johnson, why is Beeta making fun of you so badly? Hey, Electra, I don't know what's-
Oh, me?
I know, I saw, yeah, Beeta today, I went to Beeta's show and-
I don't know, she is like, she is like a whole video of me and like, she is like a picture of me, I am no clue.
Yeah, I mean
I was like the leader of the uncle fuckers. Can you give me everybody's I was not Arthur was
Was Arthur did that and it's like, you know and then and it's like of course nobody agrees with the you know with that and stuff
But today, um, let's see like Arthur came on and her show and he's like, hey was it well
I said you have nobody to chat by the way, how many people do I have my chat 52 people 49 people at like three in the morning
Okay, not too bad for me. Okay. Hey, Katie
Thank you always. So I think I think I'm my show is fine.
He's like, oh, why is he is not about how many people you get?
It's about the view. It's all about the views.
It's not about how many people you get.
You've got to see yourself from the viewership because listen,
what is coming to fucking people's heads? Listen.
Viewership have you not heard viewership viewership? Oh, I got this how many oh, I got I got a hundred people viewers
Watching me. Oh my gosh. Listen. I could have had that listen
I've never streamed one day in my life if I had streamed
I would have at least to under my first show.
Okay, that's not what I'm talking about.
Okay, if you want to go on viewership,
we all could do it, every single one of us.
Every single one of us.
And it's not about that.
It's about keeping your loyalty in.
It's about,
Yeah, it's a quality over quantity and like for example
This month was my best financial month on YouTube
and so it may have been like a little bit lower than numbers, but it's like the higher quality of people and
My so it's my best month ever on YouTube. So. Oh, thank you, Katie. I'll get on Jonathan
Are you saying like some people think that it's all about the numbers? It's not it's about your friends like, you know
Just keeping us not
And by the way guys my channel like even like with with all my I'm private a bunch of videos
And it says I have like half a million minutes
So if I am private at all my videos it probably close to a million minutes of viewership and so that's wow
That's a lot to me. It's like that's more than like the three thousand
What I'm gonna do I'm gonna keep your fucking show on all day all night as long as I can
that's what I'm saying. Thank you for fucking hours because I have
there's there are 12 hours. So, Si, Si, Si, Si, you're doing
better than most people. Don't let people like Gotti and JT
get you down. Don't do that. Yeah, and they're mad at me for
like no reason but it's like I should be mad, you know, it's
like but they're like, Oh, they're mad at you because you're
I think I am I think I'm very happy with how things are going. So we have Randy
Let me just check this. Yeah, you're real you're really doing something and JT
JT could never do this. He never could do this
It's like when you're sorry when you're going with the idea like you
Mm-hmm. Go ahead. The lady was talking the other guy was talking before me. Go ahead. It's a question about
Go ahead you guys. That's fine. You can ask. Um, I'm ready about terror. Okay, go ahead
it why don't you take the red paint off your face before you come up
it's part of a bit don't worry about it
it's fine it's fine
so anyway yeah I just like this everyday right
anyway so Psyche so let me ask you this and my astrology she just had a kid this girl I
know she's the only other knowledgeable astrology person I know that I text with some shit
So she's going through a lot in a good way. I can't really ask her about this right now
And is it normal to just literally randomly shuffle tarot cards or are there different forms to it because I saw
Without getting you know polemic or anything. There's a trans person on there's a trans person on here
I'll just say that it's not cuz they're trans, but they
They claim to do tarot
but when i've seen you do it like a lot of it is still somewhat subjective but you seem more
professional with it than the way that they do it and the way they were doing it is literally like
give me a five dollar donation and i'll reach your tower oh five dollar donation and they literally
just take cards and randomly shuffle them so is that is that like par for the course in tarot
or is that considered unprofessional because it seemed unprofessional to me i don't know
Well, why so why do you have to mention that you have kids can him a question? I was
Yeah, okay, so about the um, you know people some people dude due to terror for the donation
I mean is and I do too or no or I would appreciate hips and stuff like that
I mean, I don't but I do like the free readings, you know, some people can get as like see if like we're compatible
Yeah
it's like and so but I like to I like to offer of course free readings for the first time too
some people yeah
people have different styles there's different ways that I think the message looks like it's called fish
yeah and you look like some anonymous asshole that I can't see so shut the f*** up as I'm talking to him
and not you hillbilly all right so psyche is that I'm so I'm trying to behave man you know how they push me
yeah you're fine you're fine I'm trying to not say and or anything like that yeah thank you anyway
is that that's acceptable than to do that
is that
maybe it is acceptable
it's all different
people have different styles
I don't know who you're talking about
I don't understand why you think you could come up here
looking like this
I don't give a shit what you have to say asshole
I'm asking Psyche right now bro
if you want to talk to me like an
a man you talk to me after
get them
so Psyche is it
yeah he's a fucking asshole
so fuck him
he's a funny baby
he's the one off flying monkey
that's why
so Psyche
Yeah, let's talk about monkeys. I know I don't like them either.
You mean, you mean, get this, this guy needs to fucking be checked.
Oh, what's that, Crystal?
Well, I don't know you. What? I'm asking, I was asking Psyche a question
and this hillbilly asshole starts, you know, answering for him on his own stream, ma'am.
So I don't understand what I need to be check for. I'm asking Psyche a question.
Well, you're being disrespectful.
How? How was he? Yeah, he was disrespectful to me.
You remember talking, you're disrespecting.
You're not fucking letting him respond.
No, I did. It's just you budding in it.
And you're not fucking letting him fucking talk.
Oh, sorry.
So my camera got unplugged.
There we go.
I'm so sorry, Yumi.
I said F.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's great.
When you have something valuable to say after that.
I'll just tell you all.
Yeah, psyche.
So anyway, so different styles.
You can do that.
Well, people have different styles and it's like, and so some people are going to be more
compatible than other people.
It's just like you have to find somebody that speaks to you because there are some people
that don't take it as seriously as other people and some people are just using it as a money
making thing.
but I know paid their faces read and some people I can't see your face I can't see your face
So it's whatever. Hey, thanks, like if we're answering you see all these people fucking interrupt and claim. I'm disrespectful
That's fine. I'll fall back
You see that's like on your stream
and sexy I
Saw her two times
Yeah, I mean it's a vaccine Randy
You have like a weird name be cash has a weird name with it with a troll thing
And so I don't know who you guys are so I think I really don't know if I should have the law
I don't I just don't want people some people saying the other way
Hey, man, people listen people sorry people can interject and crystal, you know you from the South to you understand man or sonny, right? Hey
here's what it was i'm from the midwest actually i'm so sorry okay well and not too different from
the middle of america yeah no that's fine i know where the midwest is thank you for clarifying that
so all i'm saying is i was i was asking you if you could not talk over people thanks i was asking
the guy a question the other guy kept fucking interrupting i didn't appreciate that so that's
why i was disrespectful to him all right so like you're assertive with me i'm assertive with you
so if you ask me a question i'll answer you want me to be quiet ask him or her a question
I'll show you the same respect and difference. All right. That's how I am. I'll just let you know that
So there you go. Oh my gosh. So this guy's from another part of the country now. Oh yai yai yai
All right, so I get I'm being respectful. I'm a fall back
So someone's saying something about the word. Um, let's see the word they said the word uh easy said it's the word
um
It means Ma Mett or Ma Vet MAVET. Oh, and so I just think of Ma Vet. I think of like the story of the golem
Okay, okay, right Rebalor is still here the story of the golem and then so on the golem the guys like he's in Kabbalah
Right, and so he'd make he put he brings the golem to life by writing
Emmeth on his head EMETH I think and so then Emmeth means life
Then when the golem starts getting out of control he like has the golem and you know the all is about to hurt him and stuff like that
He like he has the golem like lean down and then he rubs off the e on the name
And it turns it from life into death and then the golem dies when we know I'll let you on
But yeah, we have a lot of people back seat. Yeah, I'm gonna let beat on and so you're right
You're gonna ban me if I share what's on my arm. It's not that certain group and I don't want to show it
All right. So yeah death to a certain group, but I don't want to say it
Okay, thank you
Just no, I don't have no way for you. Don't hate on me. You mean if there's like, you know people
You know people don't like me doesn't mean I don't love you
I think you're good chrystal. You're good chrystalline. I know like
We all have people we all have you know
We all have trolls and the people that will come and like you know some some trolls are like particularly don't like us and stuff
you know, um
I'm just gonna be like honest and
You know, you know, let people know how I feel exactly
But I don't really mind trolled. I know we have a lot of trolls here. I'd like to like you know, I love it
Oh, we'll do it
We gotta deal with it, you know
Exactly and we'll deal with it and it's like and we understand trolling too. I'm also I'm I'm gonna put out a book about trolling
Okay, it'll have all the
It's actually 500 pages. It'll have all the whole of yeah, we should definitely
Yeah, like some kind of like thing, you know like there's like
Per se okay per se
You know that
We are kind of in this alone, in a sense, as us, as you and I, you know, we don't bring in our family members,
but Bita brings in her family members, and then wonders why people call her uncle fuckers and stuff.
Okay, well, yeah, let's...
I don't I really don't think that's like a person to be repeated, but but no, I mean, yeah
I know but that's not I didn't start that by the way. That was all joke. That was by South Park
Yeah, yeah, it was and
Yeah, I know it is kind of like, you know a little bit
Yeah, I do remember I
Yeah, they're longer and uncut
So let's see. I mean, it's like Randy. I just have a bad feeling about Randy
I'll put up a banner. Hold on. Let me see if these people are actually here. Hold on
It's okay
Also, I was one of psyche's worst trolls and I'm kind of shocked to let me back on I was I was pretty mean to him
Oh, I was pretty bad for a few weeks